Catch it if you can!
Flubber is a comedy, family, science fiction film directed by Les Mayfield.
Professor Phillip Brainard, an absent minded professor, works with his assistant Weebo, trying to create a substance
that's a new source of energy and that will save Medfield College where his sweetheart Sara is the president.
He has missed his wedding twice, and on the afternoon of his third wedding, Professor
Brainard creates flubber, which allows objects to fly through the air.
Professor Philip Brainard, played by Robin Williams.
Dr. Sara Jean Reynolds, played by Marcia Gay Harden.
Wilson Croft, played by Christopher McDonald.
Chester Hoenicker, played by Raymond J. Barry.
Smith, played by Clancy Brown.
Secretary at Ford Motor Company, played by Nancy Olson.
Flubber is a 1997 American science-fiction comedy film directed by Les Mayfield (who had previously directed
the John Hughes scripted remake, Miracle on 34th Street) and written by Hughes and Bill Walsh.
A remake of The Absent-Minded Professor (1961), the film was produced by Walt Disney Pictures and
stars Robin Williams, Marcia Gay Harden, Christopher McDonald, Ted Levine, Raymond J.
Barry, Wil Wheaton and Clancy Brown, with Jodi Benson providing a voice.
The film was a box office success, grossing $178 million worldwide but received negative reviews from critics, with criticism for its
slapstick humor, special effects, story, script and comparisons to the original, but praised Williams’ performance.
The film explores themes of wedding vows,
inventor, slime, flight, mad scientist.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.